Kettle and Idol
Family.
I see.
Family is a broad term.
Yes, it is.
I'm embarrassed to say this, but...
I love my family.
Yes.
When I want attention, I talk to my sister a lot.
I talk to my mom.
It's like that, but it comes as a set.
But that comes with the package.
I like him so much that I don't mind that.
I see...
How far apart are your siblings?
There are five, including me.
I'm 17.
Are you the eldest?
Yes, the eldest.
And my sister is two steps younger.
I see.
Three younger.
And I have two younger brothers.
They're in the fourth grade.
Is that right?
Yes.
My brother's a little farther away from me, but my sister's pretty close.
It's fun to be that close to your sister.
It's a lot of fun.
My sister's second sister likes Stardust idols.
We talk a lot about what we think of this idol.
I often stream their performances.
It's not a lot of noise, but...
The sound of my mom's vacuum cleaner, or the sound of her cooking...
It's a bit of a hassle, isn't it?
I didn't like it at first.
That's right.
I wanted to keep it quiet.
Even the fans couldn't hear the vacuum cleaner today.
It's like, "I can't hear Mom's voice.
I guess that's what they're looking for.
Lately, it's been a little sister or something.
Oh, you have a sister? I think I'd appreciate it more if I got something like that.
I'm grateful for that.
I see.
I wonder if your mom can already hear that... from the audience.
The guests...
I'm a little...
Mom, I'm just wondering if the customers...
Are they pushing each other? Something like that.
I have a client who likes me.
But when my mom comes over, she starts saying that I'm her favorite.
So when my mom comes over, she gives me a temporary "guess".
What about your mom?
Or talk to her a little more?
Yes, like, "Do you want some water? Or something like that.
Or when I really want something, like food.
When I really want something, like food, and I can't help it, I say, "Mama.
And he'd say, "Mama, mama, mama.
And then I'd come over and I'd say something to her, and she'd comment on it.
And then they comment on it like I'm guessing.
So I don't say it like "guess who? I say something like that.
No, that's nice.
I don't think so.
Your sister's one, too, right? You mentioned earlier that she's a Starlust idol.
How do you feel about your sister's group?
She likes my group a lot.
She actively comes to our live shows.
So I'm a little concerned about her group.
She's curious.
That's why she asked me in the comments of the fans when I was distributing.
Do you have a favorite? or something like that.
If it were a scoring session, whose place would you want to go to? or "If it were a scoring meeting, who would you want to go to?
I asked my sister.
She told me that her first guess is Ayame Kawase.
Rinna Yuki is my guess.
I thought, "I'm not in it.
But she said, "Oh, I see...
Then I asked her if she wanted to go to the scoring session. I said something like that.
She said "Moa-chan".He called me "Moa-chan".
I said, "Why? I said, "Why?
He said, "I'm nervous, so the other members are not.
Like, "Oh, there you are!
You're so cute, but I really like your name.
She's a little bit cute... and very cute... my sister.
I know, right? If you were my sister, I'd be like...
Why?
I was careless.
But I ran out of hoodies the other day.
You know...
This show...
Tatsuya.
Mawaten Aoshi no Momo-san
Atsushi
Mr. Takkun
This program was provided by Mr. Marren.
Thank you very much!
By Byron